Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/aschellrn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hospitals

Surgery

Healthcare

Certifications

CCRN

NIHSS

BLS

PALS

ACLS

Angela Schell

MSHI, BSN, RN, CCRN

Saint Petersburg, Florida

Summary

Experienced critical care nurse with Neuro/Trauma ICU, cath lab and interventional experience. Independent and quick thinker able to make decisions in fast paced acute and critical care settings. Adept problem solving capabilities: individually and as a team player. Dedicated and caring nursing professional with a genuine concern for patient well-being.

Will have my Master of Science in Biomedical Health Information because of my passion to understand health information and technology challenges from all disciplines. Improving healthcare delivery requires a team approach.

Experience

U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs 2 years 1 month

Emergency Room Nurse

June 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Interventional Radiology
June 2018 - June 2019 (1 year 1 month)

Tampa, Florida

Tampa General Hospital
Radiology/Special Procedures Nurse
October 2015 - July 2018 (2 years 10 months)

BayCare Health System Interventional Radiology Nurse January 2013 - September 2015 (2 years 9 months)

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Interventional Radiology

Bayfront Medical Center

Cardiac Cath Lab RN

July 2011 - December 2012 (1 year 6 months)

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Cardiac Cath Lab and Wound Care

St. Mary's Medical Center

Cardiac Cath Lab RN

December 2008 - May 2011 (2 years 6 months)

Evansville, Indiana Area

Cardiac Cath Lab

Deaconess Health System

Trauma Critical Care RN

August 1999 - May 2009 (9 years 10 months)

Evansville, Indiana Area

Neuro Surgical and Trauma ICU

Covance

Clinical Operations Supervisor

August 2006 - April 2008 (1 year 9 months)

Evansville, Indiana Area

Clinical Research Unit Phase I and Phase II Drug Trials

St. Mary's Health

Registered Nurse

May 1995 - August 1999 (4 years 4 months)

Evansville, Indiana Area

Education

University of Illinois at Chicago

Master's of Science, Health Informatics · (2016 - 2020)

University of Southern Indiana

Bachelor's of Science, Nursing Science · (2006 - 2007)

University of Southern Indiana

ASN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1995 - 1997)

Indiana University Bloomington

Health Services/Allied Health/Health Sciences, General · (1993 - 1995)